原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨
翻译     VioletCheng  二糯米  不见陈辰
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     兜兜兜爹
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第八集
晚上好  万圣节来了又走
Good evening. Well, Halloween has come and gone
可你瞧  最近世界变得这么吓人
but, you know, the world has gotten so darn scary lately,
可怕的怪物什么的
what with the grim specter of everything,
一个假期根本不够
that one holiday just wasn't enough
容纳这么多恐惧和担心
to contain all the frights and chills.
所以今年
So this year
恐惧蔓延到了感恩节
the terror has spread into Thanksgiving.
感恩节一直都很吓人
Thanksgiving was always scary.
我们在一点还是七点吃饭
Do we eat at 1:00 or 7:00
还是  上帝啊  四点十五分
or, God forbid, 4:15?
今晚  我们带来三个让人后心发凉
Tonight, we're bringing you three spine-tingling
而且大快朵颐的感恩节恐怖故事
and stomach-filling tales of Thanksgiving terror.
挺毛骨悚然的
It's pretty gruesome,
所以你可能想挡一挡孩子的眼睛
so you might want to cover your kids' eyes.
你俩已经进入感恩节角色了
Ooh, you two have gotten into the Thanksgiving spirit.
不正确  我们正在占领你们的星球
Incorrect. We are taking over your planet.
这难道不是压迫你们的殖民者所穿的服装吗
Is this not how oppressive colonizers dress?
差不多是的
Pretty much.
晚饭几点吃
Now, what time is dinner?
没人知道
No one knows!
感恩节恐怖故事
肉汤啊
The gravy!
鸡示录[恶搞电影《启示录》]
请继续射击  好人阿卢
Prithee keep shooting, Goodman Lou.
警官  我的毛瑟枪
Uh, Constable, my musket
得占用上帝三分钟时间才能重新上膛
taketh three of the Lord's minutes to reload.
那就像你勒紧帽子一样勒死它们
Then buckle their necks as you would thine hat.
看啊  我们抓着了什么
Well, what do we haveth hither?
上帝说  "使人管理
And God sayeth, "Let man have dominion
"海里的鱼
"Over the fish of the sea,
"还有陆地上的火鸡
"But even more so the turkeys of the land,
"不管是盐水煮熟
"Whether they be brine-ed
还是做成火鸡肉干"
or dry-eth of rub."
我妹夫油炸了一只火鸡
My brother-in-law deep-fried a turkey.
费了好大力气
'Twas much toil and hardship
好不容易才成功
for scant reward.
这肯定是巫术
'Tis witchcraft, verily.
我必须洁净这座镇
I must cleanse the town...
用火
with fire.
朝圣者
The pilgrims.
有没有人可以为朝圣者考虑一下
Won't somebody please think of the pilgrims?
漏网之鸡
Free birds.
抓住他们
Skynyrd them!
稻草人
The scarecrow.
捡起来  捡起来
Get it up. Get it up!
这些臭火鸡会付出代价的
Those satanic butterballs will pay for this.
是时候来点斧牌身体喷雾了[血]
Now to create some Axe body spray.
老天爷啊
Odds bodkins!
你们以为能杀了我  是吧
Thought thou could killeth me, didth thou-th?
傻火鸡
You dumb turkeys.
那是死胡同
That's a dead end.
你们全都得在地狱里燃烧
You're all gonna burn in hell
还有天主教徒  英国国教徒
along with the Catholics, the Anglicans,
大部分路德会教友
most Lutherans and...
现在人们觉得每年
吃我们的兄弟是表达感恩的方式
我怕咱们火鸡的新黑暗纪元开始了
第二天之后的第四个周四
我在哪儿
Where am I?
你好  有人吗
Hello? Is anyone there?
这是什么地方
What is this place?
有人发疯整理的干干净净
Someone really went nuts with the decluttering.
有用了
Ooh, it's working.
侯默  怎么了  快让我出去
Homer, what's going on? Get me out of here.
好的好的  等等
Okay, okay, hold on.
厨房人工智能
使用手册
"你的虚拟助理一开始可能会很困惑
"Your virtual assistant may be confused at first
"把它认为成一个真实的人
"And think it's a real person.
"冷静地跟它解释  它只是
"Calmly explain to it that it is merely a construct
人工智能的模型"
of artificial intelligence."
虚拟助理
Virtual assistant?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你会笑的  每年  马姬都会抱怨
Okay, you're gonna laugh. Every year, Marge complains
她得为感恩节做多少吃的
about how much cooking she has to do for Thanksgiving.
-我就是马姬  -等等
- I'm Marge. - Hold on.
我正在威廉·索诺玛吃免费的薄荷巧克力
So, I'm in Williams-Sonoma eating free peppermint bark,
一个在那里工作的孩子说  我和我的太太
and the kid working there said my wife would love
一定会喜欢这个厨房人工智能
this kitchen A.I. thing.
我就是你的太太
I'm your wife.
等等  所以我就拿了一点马姬的基因
Hold on. So, I sent some of Marge's DNA
送到一家看起来清清白白的公司
to one of those innocent-seeming companies,
就像机器人杀光人类的那种电影
like from the beginning of a sci-fi movie
开头出现的一样
where the robots murder everyone.
然后他们给了我她的电脑版
And it sent us a computer version of her
解决所有做饭的问题
to do all the cooking,
就是你
and that's you!
对了  你住在这个小管子里
Oh, yeah. And you live in that tube thingy.
你是说我是个仿真版本吗
Are you saying that I'm a simulation?
不  这太疯狂了
No. That's insane.
不再是了
Not anymore.
可信到恐怖
Just chillingly plausible.
好吧  我看得出来你需要一些时间
Okay, I can see you're gonna need some time
才能搞明白
to come to terms with finding out
你只是一堆1和0组成的
you're just a bunch of ones and zeros.
对  对
Uh, yeah. Yeah.
所以这上面说
So, this says
我可以让你在里面经历两周的时间
I can make you experience two weeks in there
外面却只过了两秒
in only two seconds out here.
怎么样
So?
在经过两周的虚无之后  你感觉怎么样了
How you feeling after two weeks of nothing but nothingness?
我以为再也见不到第二个人了
I-I thought I'd never see another soul
永远见不到了
for all eternity.
独处的时间什么都比不上
Nothing like a little me time.
你现在冷静下来了吗
So, you cool now?
我冷静了  我冷静了
I'm cool. I'm cool.
-超级冷静  -那就好
- So cool. - That's cool.
好了  马姬  它全都设置好了
Okay, Marge! It's all set up.
我不是"它"
I'm not an "it."
我就是"它"
I'm an "It."
我非常喜欢被称为"它"
I love being an "it."
"它"有什么能为你效劳
How can "it" Help?
我喜欢它的态度
Oh, I like its attitude.
太有帮助了
So helpful.
那我就不打扰你为两位女士
Then I'll leave you two lovely ladies
与人工智能相识了
to get A.I.-quainted.
可信到恐怖
Chillingly plausible.
这难道不会非常有趣吗  一起做饭
Isn't this going to be fun, cooking together?
我的确喜欢做饭
Well, I do love to cook.
没有比我自己更好的伙伴了
And who better than with myself?
不如我们从简单的东西开始吧
Why don't we start with something easy,
比如给孩子们做午饭
like making the kids lunch.
巴仔的最爱是芝士通心粉
Bart's favorite is macaroni and cheese.
加热狗和水果圈
With hot dogs and Froot Loops.
关于我们这位特别的小朋友
I know everything you know
你知道的我全都知道
about our special little guy.
对  你就是我
Oh. Right, you're me.
我是你
I'm you.
披萨外卖
午饭真棒  机器人妈妈
Awesome lunch, robot Mom.
我吃过的最棒的芝士通心粉加热狗水果圈
Best cheesy-mac-fruit-dog I've ever had.
这些薄饼的蓬松程度可一点都不虚
There's nothing virtual about the fluffiness of these pancakes.
-谢谢  -记住
- Thank you. - Well, remember,
这东西使用了我的记忆才知道你们喜欢什么
that thing used my memories to know what you like.
所以她才能完美地替换掉你
Which is why she's an awesome replacement for you.
所以你真的知道我知道的一切吗
So, you really know everything I know?
对  要不然我怎么做你的完美助理
Yep. How else could I be your perfect helper?
你记得我第一次吻侯默吗
Do you remember the first time I kissed Homer?
他的口气有啤酒和加油站里的玉米片的味道
His breath smelled like beer and gas station nachos.
对
Oh, yeah.
诡异  太诡异了
It's creepy. It's just creepy.
我知道的她都知道  比我知道的还多
She knows everything I know. More than I know.
宝贝  那可是威廉·索诺玛
Honey, it's Williams Sonoma.
他们不会误导我们的
They wouldn't steer us wrong.
我们的帕尼尼机就是在那买的
That's where we got our panini press.
帕尼尼机可不会记得
The panini press doesn't remember me
我在夏令营弄湿了床铺
wetting my bunk at summer camp.
有什么大不了的  她就是个有无限耐心的
What's the big deal? She's just an infinitely patient,
永远不会变老的你
never-aging version of you.
你善于让女人觉得她很特别
You really know how to make a woman feel special.
真漂亮
Oh, that's beautiful.
我看不见你反对的表情
And I can't see your disapproving look
因为你压根没法做表情
because you don't have a face.
你善于让女人觉得她很特别
You really know how to make a woman feel special.
谢谢  机器人宝贝
Thanks, robot honey.
就叫我马姬吧
Just call me Marge.
马姬
Marge.
你知道吗  我一直觉得
You know, I always thought
你最性感的地方就是声音
the sexiest thing about you was your voice.
你还有什么想对我说的吗
Is there anything else you want to say to me?
辛普森先生  你在和我调情吗
Mr. Simpson, are you flirting with me?
我不觉得有什么不妥
I don't see what's wrong.
我是你丈夫
I am your husband.
既然如此
Well, in that case...
最棒的是...
...the most incredible...
然后我还要...
...and then I'm going to...
管子里的老婆  你最清楚我想要什么了
Oh, tube-wife, you know exactly what I want.
亲爱的  这说明不了什么
Honey, it didn't mean anything.
只不过是几块半夜的猪排
They were just midnight pork chops.
老实说  比我做的好吃吗
Be honest. Were they better than mine?
是的
Yes!
Yes.
原谅我  它们太美味了
Forgive me. They were exquisite.
好了  够了  把她弄走
Okay, enough. Get rid of her.
-我意思是"它"  -我做不到
- I mean "It." - I can't.
她和我  你选一个
It's her or me.
好吧  我会删了虚拟的你
Aw, fine. I'll delete virtual you.
删了我  不行  不行
Delete me? No. No!
等等  等等  这样会伤着她吗
Wait, wait, wait. Will that hurt her?
会啊  我加了钱能让它感受到疼痛
Oh, yeah. I paid extra for it to feel pain.
不  这样不对
No, it's not right.
-别删她了  -太好了
- Don't delete her. - Yes!
感恩节过后再说吧
Till after Thanksgiving.
虚拟的我要给我们全家人和朋友
Virtual me is going to make Thanksgiving dinner
做感恩节晚餐
for all our family and friends.
然后我就永久抹去她
Then I'll erase her forever.
我不是虚拟的  我是真实的
I'm not virtual. I'm real.
我得从这里出去
I've got to get out of here.
对了
Of course.
我能连上网络
My link to the Internet.
防火墙
A firewall?
我被困在这个蠢管子里了
I'm trapped in this stupid tube.
明天就是感恩节了
Thanksgiving's tomorrow.
我需要时间想想怎么逃出去
I need time to think of a way to escape.
就是这个  时间
That's it. Time.
八年的独自思考时间正好够我
Eight years alone with my thoughts was just the right amount of time
想出完美的逃脱方案了
to come up with the perfect escape plan.
第一步  做出我的家人还有那女人
Step one, cook the best Thanksgiving dinner
吃过的最棒的感恩节晚餐
my family and that woman ever had.
这么丰盛
What a spread.
难以置信这些都是你自己做的
I can't believe you did all this by yourself.
马姬  你简直就是个烹饪机器
Marge, you are a cooking machine.
这顿大餐的确很费功夫  但是能和大家
Well, this meal was a lot of work, but having us together
一起度过感恩之日  我愿意再做一次
to share this day of thanks, I'd do it all again.
那个婊子
That bitch.
好了  好了  第二步
Okay, okay. Step two.
在他们吃我做的大餐时  我去做点有用的事
While they're eating my meal, I get some feet on the ground.
好了  我的小R2
Okay, R2#MeToo,
R2-D2是《星球大战》中经常扭转乾坤的小机器人
#MeToo是社交媒体上呼吁人们说出真相的标签  "我也是"
带我奔向自由吧  过道衣柜里的调制解调器
carry me to freedom: the modem in the hall closet.
我成功了
I made it.
甜美的网络自由
Sweet Internet freedom.
晚餐结束了
Dinner's over.
现在该删掉你了
Now to delete you,
我就能退回这发明  换商店抵用券了
so I can return this gizmo for store credit.
赶快  宝贝  把妈妈拿到柜子里的盒子旁边
Quick, sweetie, carry Mommy to that box in the closet.
阿麦  别去
Maggie, stop!
那只是个假的妈妈
That's just a make-believe Mommy.
我不能拥抱你
I can't hug you,
但我能发出你听见的第一种声音
but I can play the first sound you ever heard.
我的心跳声
My heartbeat.
我自由了
I'm free!
最后一件事
Just one last thing.
晚餐是我做的  我  机器人我
I made the dinner! Me, the robot!
马姬什么都没做
Marge did nothing.
马姬  你怎么这样子
Marge, how could you?
社交评分
马姬
社交评分暴跌
Social rating nosediving.
急转直下
Nosediving.
我打嗝都是谎言的味道
My burps taste like lies.
阿麦更喜欢虚拟的我
Maggie chose a virtual me over me.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
世界进步模糊了人类和科技的界限
Our world blurs the line between humanity and technology.
我们问"这件事能做到吗"
Our society asks "Can we do it?"
而不是"这件事该做吗"
Instead of "Should we do it?"
但别担心  我还爱你
But don't worry. I still love you,
爱你  爱你  爱你
love you, love you, love you,
-爱你  爱你  -太闹心了吧
- love you, love you... - Well, this makes
变成机器人了你还是忘记给我生日礼物
you forgetting my birthday even worse.
国家地理  维鸡百科  可汗学院
太空网  史密森博物馆
Etsy电商
全人类的知识宝库等我探索
I have all of humanity's knowledge to explore.
蕴含了文明启蒙的无限可能
And limitless possibilities for enlightenment.
去这里
To Etsy.
老式打字机做的花盆  这是天堂吗
A planter made from an old typewriter? I'm in heaven.
最后的感恩节
航行日志  星际殖民舰队
Ship's log, interplanetary colonization vessel
人类的希望
Humanity's Hope.
我们距离地球已经一千光年了
Earth is a thousand light-years behind us,
如果地球还在的话
if there even is an Earth anymore.
全球变暖毁灭世界之后
After global warming ravaged our world,
我们不再使用矿物燃料  控制了污染
we eliminated fossil fuels and reduced pollution,
让地球冷却
cooling down the planet
导致了大规模冰河时代的来临
and thereby triggering a massive ice age.
不过最后一艘飞船幸存了
But one last ship escaped
暴雪飓风和冰冻火山爆发
the snow hurricanes and ice volcanoes,
带着在遥远世界开启新生活的希望
buoyed by the hope of a new start
漂浮在宇宙中
on a faraway world.
孩子们  你们好
Greetings, children.
你看到这个的时候  我早就死了
If you are seeing this, I'm long dead.
你们先于家长们从休眠中被唤醒
You have been de-hibernated from hypersleep
来负责飞船的日常维护
before your parents to perform routine ship maintenance
并继续完成"文明的末路"模型作业
and complete your end-of-civilization dioramas.
睁大眼睛看巴仔  所有人  今天可是感恩节
Eyes Bart-wise, everyone. Today's Thanksgiving.
我们努力工作  睡了这么多年
We've worked hard, sleeping for so many years.
难道不该来场宴会吗
Don't we deserve a feast?
我们可以把发酵面团
I suppose we could sculpt
雕刻成火鸡的形状
our yeast paste into the shape of a turkey.
呕  应该有比这更好的主意
Ew. We can do better than that.
这艘飞船上有建立新文明所需的一切
This ship has all the stuff on it to start a new civilization.
肯定也有感恩节食物
There's got to be some Thanksgiving grub here somewhere.
农业复兴计划
"全气候适应型小麦芽"
"All-climate wheat crop germination..."
无聊
Oh. Boring.
"地球最后的番茄种子"
"Earth's last tomato seeds."
这是夏天的食物
Eh, those are more of a summer food.
快看这是啥
Hello. What do we have here?
沼泽女王
果冻型蔓越莓酱
蔓越莓酱  这才是我想要的
Cranberry sauce. Huh, now we're talking.
-但只有一罐  -很快就不是了
- But it's only one can. - Not for long.
只要把果酱放进这台老式物质复制机里
We just chuck this can of cran in the old matter replicator.
咻嗖唰  我们马上就能在果酱里游泳了
Zip-zap-zorp and we'll be swimming in sauce.
咻  嗖  唰
警告  警告
Warning, warning!
作为全飞船唯一的科学顾问
As the ship's holo science officer,
我必须提醒你  这台机器只能用于复制
I must caution you that this machine was only designed
无机物
to replicate inorganic matter:
螺丝钉  法兰盘
bolts, flanges,
歌颂各州首府的时尚顶针
dainty thimbles celebrating the state capitals.
如果试图复制生物材料  你
But if you attempt to replicate biological material, y...
跳过广告
Skip ad.
活着就会生不如死
...and the living will envy the dead.
复制
这破玩意儿坏了
Aw, the crummy thing doesn't work.
这是史上最烂的最后的感恩节了
This is the worst last Thanksgiving ever.
快看
Look.
哇  它活了
Whoa. It's alive.
他真是个可爱的小家伙
Aw. He's a cute little guy.
你是吗  小可爱  是吗
Aren't you, fella? Aren't you? Yeah.
真恶心
Gross!
我们把一罐蔓越莓酱放进了复制器里
We put a can of cranberry sauce into the replicator,
然后它突变成了一个果冻怪物
and it mutated into a jelly monster.
看看它把我的胳膊搞成什么样了
Look what it did to my arm.
看招
Arm wedgie!
真棒  现在你把我胳膊抻长了
Great, now you stretched it out.
真是谢谢你了
Thanks a lot.
我们得找到果冻怪物然后除掉它
We got to find the jelly monster and kill it.
等会等会
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
这个"怪物"之所以这么暴躁
The "Monster" probably only lashed out
也许是因为你太有攻击性了
because you met it with aggression.
生物伦理规程里关于第一次接触
The bioethical protocols of first contact
有着明确的
clearly state that...
杀了这怪物  快杀了它
Kill the monster! Kill the monster!
这回轮到你了
Haw-haw.
为什么怪物要吃我们的骨头
What does the jelly want with our skeletons?
原来如此
Of course.
果冻是用明胶做的  明胶是由骨头制成的
Jelly's made of gelatin, which comes from bones,
所以这个怪物专挑骨头吃
so the creature's gonna feed wherever the most bones are.
吃吧吃吧  不要害羞
Gobble, gobble, don't be jerky.
配上甘薯  享用火鸡
Pass the yams and carve the turkey.
-快跑  你们有危险  -快出来  快跑
- Get out! Go! You're in danger! - Get out of there! Run!
-快点跑啊  快跑  -你们很危险
- Get the hell out! Go, go, man! - You're in danger!
吃吧吃吧  不要害羞
Gobble, gobble, don't be jerky.
配上甘薯  享用火鸡
Pass the yams and carve the turkey.
太可惜了
Aw, it's a shame.
这怪物不知道人皮才是最好吃的吗
Doesn't that thing know the skin's the best part?
我们该怎么办
What are we gonna do?
总不能一直躲在这里
We can't hide in this closet forever.
我们死定了
We're all dead, man.
它会吃掉你的骨头  还有你的骨头
It's gonna eat your skelly, and your skelly.
它会把我们的骨头都吃光
It's gonna eat all our skellies!
多谢了  我正需要这一下
Thanks. I needed that.
我是马丁  让我进去
It's Martin. Let me in.
我黑进了一艘逃生舱
I've hacked into an escape pod.
我们可以一起逃离这里
We can all get out of here.
就快到了  快到了
Almost there. Almost there.
这果冻给自己造了个罐子
The jelly built itself a can.
你在干什么  这下我们被困住了
What are you doing? We're trapped.
看啊  完美的罐子配上完美的有机体
Behold, the perfect can for the perfect organism.
你  你竟然仰慕它
You, you admire it.
我欣赏它的纯粹  没有丑陋的人性
I admire its purity, its lack of messy humanity.
这个你们称之为"怪物"的东西
This creature, as you call it,
不被人类这将灭种族坚持的可笑道德观束缚
is unencumbered by the petty morality of a dying species.
我将献出我的躯体与这完美的
I giveth my body to become one with the ideal...
你们看到了吗
You know what?
它刚刚害怕了
I think it's just scared.
小家伙  没事的
Hey, little guy. It's okay.
没人会伤害你的
No one's gonna hurt you.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be okay...
苗浩斯的计划奏效了  它分心了
Milhouse's plan is working. It's distracted.
我不是这么计划的
This wasn't my plan!
我们得把它引到气闸那里
We need to lure it into the air lock.
鼻涕怪奥斯卡
Hey, Oscar the Glop,
我们要把你的宝贝罐子
we're gonna shoot your precious trash can
发射到太阳真正升起的地方  外太空
where the sun does shine: outer space.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
我们做到了
We made it.
-我们安全了  -快看那边
- We're safe. - Look, over there.
-侯默  -妈妈
- Homer! - Mom!
现在这里就是我们的新家了
So, this is our new planet.
无线网密码是什么
What's the Wi-Fi password?
这渗人的红雨是怎么回事
What's with all the crazy red rain?
是吃剩的果冻
Leftovers!
卟啦嘎
Blarg.
卟啦嘎  卟啦嘎  卟啦嘎
Blarg, blarg, blarg.
卟啦嘎  卟啦嘎
Blarg. Blarg.
真美味  小孩的骨头
Mmm. Children's bones.
故事的最后  蔓越莓果冻怪物
In the end, the cranberry jelly monster
终于找到了自己的归宿  并不是吃掉别人
finally found peace, not in eating others,
而是被别人吃掉
but in having others eat it.
看起来它真正想要的  不过是做一道配菜而已
It seems all it really wanted was to be a side dish.
第一个卟啦嘎恩节